jumpstartviews.com 2013-06-07

# Terms of Use, Privacy Policy, Refund Policy

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

What information do we save?

-Your name  
-Your email  
-Any other info visible on Dashboard (videos, twitter, facebook)  
-Your most recent IP 

We don't keep

-Your phone number  
-Your address  
-Your payment information

We do have access to your phone number, address and financial information for a brief moment after you place an order, however the server discards all the information and doesn't save it anywhere. This is partially because of security reasons, partially because we simply don't care about your address/phone number/payment info.

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required toï¿½keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be kept on file for more than 60 days.

### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone or by contacting customer service.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.jumpstartviews.com

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy. 

JumpStart will, at its discretion, allow for the return or replacement of any defective product or service within 60 days from the date of purchase. For recurring billing products, returns for more than one payment may be provided if requested within the standard 60 day return period. After 60 days all sales are final.

By registering an account you acknowledge to the following JumpStart terms and conditions. Please read all of it carefully before registering a new account. This terms of service document (TOS) will explain your relationship with JumpStart and how your information will be used. This is a binding contract between you and JumpStart LLC. If any modifications are made to this TOS, you will be notified via email and will require a re-agreement confirmation to continue using JumpStart's services. 

### 1\. Service Usage

1.1 Your use of JumpStart products, software, services and web sites (referred to collectively as the "Services" in this document and excluding any services provided to you by JumpStart under a separate written agreement) is subject to the terms of a legal agreement between you and the JumpStart developer(s). 1.2 By registering an account on the JumpStart web site, you are automatically agreeing to JumpStart's general terms of usage (this document). 

### 2\. Collection of Information & Privacy

2.1 Any personal information (Name & Email) you provide will remain property of JumpStart. Your data will never be spread nor sold to any third parties. 2.2 Video submission information will not be saved and will never be disclosed to anyone without written consent from the owner. 2.3 You agree to the use of your data in accordance with JumpStart's privacy policies. 

### 3\. Association with YouTube

3.1 You acknowledge that JumpStart is not affiliated with YouTube LLC nor Google Inc and therefore cannot be liable for any account terminations or unnatural decisions made by the first party. 3.2 YouTube and its logos are trademarks of Google Inc. The images displayed on this web site are for illustration purposes only. 

### 4\. Liability

4.1 SUBJECT TO OVERALL PROVISION IN PARAGRAPH 3.1 ABOVE, YOU EXPRESSLY UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT JUMPSTART, ITS SUBSIDIARIES AND AFFILIATES, AND ITS LICENSORS SHALL NOT BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR: (A) ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL CONSEQUENTIAL OR EXEMPLARY DAMAGES WHICH MAY BE INCURRED BY YOU, HOWEVER CAUSED AND UNDER ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY.. THIS SHALL INCLUDE, BUT NOT BE LIMITED TO, ANY LOSS OF PROFIT (WHETHER INCURRED DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY), ANY LOSS OF GOODWILL OR BUSINESS REPUTATION, ANY LOSS OF DATA SUFFERED, COST OF PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES, OR OTHER INTANGIBLE LOSS; (B) ANY LOSS OR DAMAGE WHICH MAY BE INCURRED BY YOU, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO LOSS OR DAMAGE AS A RESULT OF: (I) ANY RELIANCE PLACED BY YOU ON THE COMPLETENESS, ACCURACY OR EXISTENCE OF ANY ADVERTISING, OR AS A RESULT OF ANY RELATIONSHIP OR TRANSACTION BETWEEN YOU AND ANY ADVERTISER OR SPONSOR WHOSE ADVERTISING APPEARS ON THE SERVICES; (II) ANY CHANGES WHICH JUMPSTART MAY MAKE TO THE SERVICES, OR FOR ANY PERMANENT OR TEMPORARY CESSATION IN THE PROVISION OF THE SERVICES (OR ANY FEATURES WITHIN THE SERVICES); (III) THE DELETION OF, CORRUPTION OF, OR FAILURE TO STORE, ANY CONTENT AND OTHER COMMUNICATIONS DATA MAINTAINED OR TRANSMITTED BY OR THROUGH YOUR USE OF THE SERVICES; (III) YOUR FAILURE TO KEEP YOUR PASSWORD OR ACCOUNT DETAILS SECURE AND CONFIDENTIAL; 4.2 THE LIMITATIONS ON JUMPSTART'S LIABILITY TO YOU IN PARAGRAPH ABOVE SHALL APPLY WHETHER OR NOT JUMPSTART HAS BEEN ADVISED OF OR SHOULD HAVE BEEN AWARE OF THE POSSIBILITY OF ANY SUCH LOSSES ARISING. 

### 5\. External Content

5.1 The Services may include hyperlinks to other web sites or content or resources. JumpStart may have no control over any web sites or resources which are provided by companies or persons other than JumpStart and its sister web sites. 5.2 You acknowledge and agree that JumpStart is not responsible for the availability of any such external sites or resources, and does not endorse any advertising, products or other materials on or available from such web sites or resources. 5.3 You acknowledge and agree that JumpStart is not liable for any loss or damage which may be incurred by you as a result of the availability of those external sites or resources, or as a result of any reliance placed by you on the completeness, accuracy or existence of any advertising, products or other materials on, or available from, such web sites or resources. *Even though JumpStart is AdSense safe, we do not recommend using it on any AdSense videos as we cannot control ad clicks or track click-bombs from any of our human traffic.
